UNITED UNIVERSITY PROFESSIONS (UUP) RECORDS (APAP039) 1964-2000
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Subgroup VII: Labor Relations-Correspondence, 1972-1993; 10; 2.0
  - Series 2: SUNY [RESTRICTED], 1972 August-1993 June; 10.2; 1.0
    - Villa, Joyce Yaple (Director of Employee Relations; Assistant Vice Chancellor for Employee Relations) [RESTRICTED], 1979 November-1983 August (Box VII.2.1, Folder 23)
    - Villa, Joyce Yaple (Director of Employee Relations; Assistant Vice Chancellor for Employee Relations) [RESTRICTED], 1983 September-1992 September (Box VII.2.1, Folder 24)
    - Wharton, Clifton (Chancellor) [RESTRICTED], 1977 October-1981 July (Box VII.2.1, Folder 25)
    - Wharton, Clifton (Chancellor) [RESTRICTED], 1981 August-1983 September (Box VII.2.1, Folder 26)
    - Wharton, Clifton (Chancellor) [RESTRICTED], 1986 January-1987 January (Box VII.2.1, Folder 27)
    - Other Correspondents (Kevin Berry, UUP Executive Director file) [RESTRICTED], 1974-1976 (Box VII.2.1, Folder 28)
    - Other Correspondents [RESTRICTED], 1972 August-1982 September (Box VII.2.1, Folder 29)
    - Other Correspondents (including 1986 correspondence on SUNY Women's Conference) [RESTRICTED], 1982 October-1983 November; 1986 October-1986 November (Box VII.2.1, Folder 30)
    - Other Correspondents [RESTRICTED], 1987 March-1988 October (Box VII.2.1, Folder 31)
- Subgroup VIII: Communications, 1973-2000; 11; 21.35
  Arranged in ten series.
  - Series 1:The Connection, 1987 September-2000 June; 11.1; 0.20
    A single page, two-sided newsletter for chapter leaders, chapter newsletter editors, delegates, Executive Board members, and committee members, printed approximately monthly on an academic year basis (i.e., September to June). As of the late 1990s, the circulation of The Connection was approximately one thousand, but chapter newsletter editors are permitted and explicitly encouraged to reprint any materials. Topics receiving regular attention include negotiations updates; member benefits information; SUNY system issues, including the SUNY budget; information on upcoming meetings and Delegate Assemblies; reports on campus specific issues of interest and/or concern to all; reports on political activism and lobbying activities; information on advertising campaigns; upcoming NYSUT and AFT conventions; and information on grant opportunities.
    For earlier versions of communications between UUP and its leadership, see the issues of For Your Information in Series 4 of Subgroup II and the Leadership Bulletins in the subject files for the Wakshull Administration in Subseries 3.1 of Subgroup III.
    - Volume 1, Nos. 1-10, 1987 September-1988 June (Box VIII.1.1, Folder 1)
    - Volume 2, Nos. 1-11, 1988 August-1989 June (Box VIII.1.1, Folder 2)
    - Volume 3, Nos. 1-9, 1989 September-1990 June (Box VIII.1.1, Folder 3)
    - Volume 4, Nos. 1-9, 1990 September-1991 June (Box VIII.1.1, Folder 4)
    - Volume 5, Nos. 1-9, 1991 September-1992 June (Box VIII.1.1, Folder 5)
    - Volume 6, Nos. 1-9, 1992 September-1993 June (Box VIII.1.1, Folder 6)
    - Volume 7, Nos. 1-9, 1993 September-1994 June (Box VIII.1.1, Folder 7)
    - Volume 8, Nos. 1-9, 1994 September-1995 July (Box VIII.1.1, Folder 8)
    - Volume 9, Nos. 1-8, 1995 September-1996 June (Box VIII.1.1, Folder 9)
    - Volume 10, Nos. 1-8, 1996 September-1997 June (Box VIII.1.1, Folder 10)
    - Volume 11, Nos. 1-9, 1997 September-1998 June (Box VIII.1.1, Folder 11)
    - Volume 12, Nos. 1-9, 1998 September-1999 June (Box VIII.1.1, Folder 12)
    - Volume 13, Nos. 1-9, 1999 September-2000 June (Box VIII.1.1, Folder 13)
  - Series 2:The Voice, 1973 May-2000 May/June; 11.2; 1.53
    The Voice is the official publication of UUP distributed to all members of the bargaining unit. In addition, complimentary copies are distributed to top-level members of SUNY management, lawmakers, and news media organizations in the state. Published on an academic year basis (i.e., each volume runs roughly from August or September to May or June), The Voice regularly carries candidate statements, information on statewide and Delegate Assembly elections, the annual audit, attendance reports for affiliate conventions, and verbatim text of negotiations proposals made by both the State and UUP. Regularly featured topics include contract negotiations with the State of New York; Executive Board activities; chapter events and issues; the SUNY budget and legislative issues affecting SUNY and higher education; increases in membership; advertising campaigns; feature articles on particular campuses, and/or specific departments or individuals on campus; information on candidates UUP endorses for state and national offices; and messages from UUP's leadership, including columns by UUP's President and reports on the President's activities.
    The Voice also carries photographs of Delegate Assemblies, lobbying activities and rallies, negotiations and other meetings, and individual officers and members. In fall 1998 [volume 26] The Voice changed from a newspaper format to a news magazine layout, and became more theme-related with a series of articles devoted to each issue's main theme, such as the concerns of part-time employees, women and the labor movement, academic freedom, and SUNY-specific features such as technology, the performing arts, and athletics on SUNY campuses. A few of the earliest volumes of The Voice are incomplete.
    Arranged chronologically by size.
    - Volume 5, Nos. 1-9, 1976 October-1977 July (Box VIII.2.1, Folder 1)
    - Volume 9, No. 10, 1981 August (Box VIII.2.1, Folder 2)
    - Volume 10, Nos. 1-8, 1981 October-1982 September (Box VIII.2.1, Folder 3)
    - Volume 11, Nos. 1-7, 1982 October-1983 June (Box VIII.2.1, Folder 4)
    - Volume 12, Nos. 1-8, 1984 July-1984 August (Box VIII.2.1, Folder 5)
    - Volume 13, Nos. 1-3, 5-6, 1984 September-1984 December; 1985 April-1985 June (Box VIII.2.1, Folder 6)
    - Volume 6, Nos. 1-10, 1977 August-1978 July (Box VIII.2.2, Folder 1)
    - Volume 7, Nos. 1-10, 1978 September-1979 August (Box VIII.2.2, Folder 2)
    - Volume 8, Nos. 1-10, 1979 September-1980 July (Box VIII.2.2, Folder 3)
    - Volume 9, Nos. 1-9, 1980 September-1981 May (Box VIII.2.2, Folder 4)
      No. 10 filed separately-Box VIII.2.5.
    - Volume 13, No. 4, 1985 February-1985 March (Box VIII.2.2, Folder 5)
    - Volume 14, Nos. 1-7, 1985 September-1986 July (Box VIII.2.3, Folder 1)
    - Volume 15, Nos. 1-16, 1986 September-1988 July (Box VIII.2.3, Folder 2)
    - Volume 16, Nos. 1-9, 1988 September-1989 June (Box VIII.2.3, Folder 3)
    - Volume 17, Nos. 1-10, 1989 September-1990 June (Box VIII.2.3, Folder 4)
    - Volume 18, Nos. 1-9, 1990 September-1991 May (Box VIII.2.3, Folder 5)
    - Volume 19, Nos. 1-9, 1991 September-1992 May (Box VIII.2.3, Folder 6)
    - Volume 20, Nos. 1-9, 1992 September-1993 May (Box VIII.2.4, Folder 1)
    - Volume 21, Nos. 1-9, 1993 September-1994 May (Box VIII.2.4, Folder 2)
    - Volume 22, Nos. 1-9, 1994 September-1995 May (Box VIII.2.4, Folder 3)
    - Volume 23, Nos. 1-9, 1995 September-1996 May (Box VIII.2.4, Folder 4)
    - Volume 24, Nos. 1-9, 1996 September-1997 May (Box VIII.2.4, Folder 5)
    - Volume 25, Nos. 1-9, 1997 September-1998 May (Box VIII.2.4, Folder 6)
    - Volume 1, Nos. 1-12, 1973 May-1974 May (Box VIII.2.5, Folder 1)
    - Volume 2, Nos. 1-12, 1974 June-1975 May (Box VIII.2.5, Folder 2)
    - Volume 3, Nos. 1-6 (8 issues total), 1975 June-1976 Summer (Box VIII.2.5, Folder 3)
    - Volume 4, No. 1, 1976 September (Box VIII.2.5, Folder 4)
    - Volume 5, Nos. 1-9, 1976 October-1977 July; (photocopies) (Box VIII.2.5, Folder 5)
    - Volume 9, No. 10, 1981 August; (photocopy) (Box VIII.2.5, Folder 6)
    - Volume 10, Nos. 1-8, 1981 October-1982 September; (photocopies) (Box VIII.2.5, Folder 7)
    - Volume 11, Nos. 1-7, 1982 October-1983 June; (photocopies) (Box VIII.2.5, Folder 8)
    - Volume 12, Nos. 1-8, 1983 August-1984 July (Box VIII.2.5, Folder 9)
    - Volume 13, Nos. 1-3, 5-6, 1984 September-1985 June (Box VIII.2.5, Folder 10)
    - Volume 26, Nos. 1-9, 1998 September-1999 June (Box VIII.2.5, Folder 11)
    - Volume 27, Nos. 1-9, 1999 September-2000 June (Box VIII.2.5, Folder 12)
  - Series 2A: News Releases, 1977 February-2000 June; 11.3; 0.33
    Press releases distributed by UUP. Topics include upcoming Delegate Assemblies; resolutions adopted at Delegate Assemblies; election results for UUP statewide officers; awards given by UUP, such as the Link Scholarship, Friend of SUNY Award, and Nina Mitchell Award; commencement and completion of contract negotiations as well as delays in negotiations and critical issues in negotiations; commentary of UUP regarding SUNY and State of New York actions (for example, the state budget or the appointment of a new Chancellor) that impact SUNY; UUP-sponsored conferences and events; and other issues that UUP wished to make its position clear on. See Subgroup II UUP Predecessors and Early UUP Years, Series 2 SPA/UUP Administrative Office General Office Files for news releases prior to 1977.
    - News Releases, 1977 February-1983 February (Box VIII.2A.1, Folder 1)
    - News Releases, 1985 June; 1986 October-1989 October (Box VIII.2A.1, Folder 2)
    - News Releases, 1989 December-1992 October (Box VIII.2A.1, Folder 3)
    - News Releases, 1993 February-1995 January (Box VIII.2A.1, Folder 4)
    - News Releases, 1995 February-1996 June (Box VIII.2A.1, Folder 5)
    - News Releases, 1996 October-1998 June (Box VIII.2A.1, Folder 6)
    - News Releases, 1998 October-2000 June (Box VIII.2A.1, Folder 7)
  - Series 3: Publications, 1978-2000; 11.4; 1.03
    - Subseries 3.1 - Legislative Ad Campaigns, 1985; 1989-2000; 11.4.1; 0.20
      Advertisements produced by UUP to coincide with sessions of the state legislature and to raise public awareness of SUNY's needs. Campaigns often focused on the impact of budget cuts on SUNY students and the impact the SUNY system has on the future of New York State. Some "legislative giveaways" carrying the legislative campaign message, as well as some oversized versions of various campaigns are included with the memorabilia in Series 9 of this Subgroup. Television and radio advertisements that accompanied various advertising campaigns are included in the video and audio tapes in Series 6 of this Subgroup. Tentative dates were assigned for some of the materials in this subseries based on information provided by members of UUP's Communications Department.
      - "Employers in New York have the SUNY advantage", ca. February 1985 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 1)
      - "We're solving one of the most urgent problems of our time: the affordable education", ca. February 1985 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 2)
      - "Who's Giving Whom the Business?", March 1985 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 3)
      - "New York, You Can't Have it Both Ways", January 1989 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 4)
      - "If You Really Love NY, Don't Cut the SUNY Budget", February 1989 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 5)
      - "We made a promise to the next generation-Can our state afford to break it?", February/March 1989; January 1990 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 6)
      - "Cancelled-How smart can New York be if we keep cutting classes?", March 1989 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 7)
      - "They're Cutting Out Classes...", March 1989 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 8)
      - "Get Smart, New York. Invest in SUNY", March 1990 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 9)
      - "Cancelled: Will SUNY Be There for the Next Generation?", December 1990 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 10)
      - Resolution condemning Gov. Cuomo on trying to break state employee union contracts, December 1990 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 11)
      - "Get the Facts", pre-1991 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 12)
      - "Nobody likes to pay higher taxes. But the alternatives are worse...", ca. 1991 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 13)
      - "Shortchanging higher education is bad business", March 1991 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 14)
      - "Cutting SUNY is the no-brain approach to solving our state's problems", March 1991 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 15)
      - "Slamming the door at SUNY slams the door on our state's future", May 1991; August 1991 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 16)
      - "State University of New York: Our Future Depends on It", January 1992 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 17)
      - "SUNY: New York's Future Depends on It", January 1992 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 18)
      - "Denied Admission", January/February 1992 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 19)
      - "Going, Going, Gone", March 1992 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 20)
      - "SUNY's Future in Question: You Hold the Answer", May 1992 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 21)
      - "Time is Running Out", June 1992 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 22)
      - "Sign and mail this letter Now-Your kid's future is at stake", ca. 1992 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 23)
      - "Under Destruction: It's time to say...No More Cuts", (Stony Brook Chapters funded), ca. 1992 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 24)
      - "A Smaller SUNY Means a Smaller New York", January 1993 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 25)
      - "Endangered Species: Invest in SUNY", January-March 1993 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 26)
      - "Infrastructure: Invest in SUNY", January-March 1993 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 27)
      - "Invest in Futures", January/February 1994 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 28)
      - "Chain Reaction: Break the Chain. Restore SUNY Funding", January/February 1995 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 29)
      - "SUNY-New York's Most Intelligent Investment", February 1995 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 30)
      - "This is not what New York voted for: Don't cut SUNY and CUNY", May 1995 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 31)
      - "This Transaction Made Possible by SUNY", October 1995-February 1996 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 32)
      - "Let's Not Lose SUNY Piece by Piece", January/February 1996 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 33)
      - "The Cuts to SUNY Affect More Than Students...", January/February 1996 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 34)
      - "Let's Not Lose SUNY Piece by Piece", sponsored by SUNY Environmental Science & Forestry, SUNY Cortland, SUNY Oswego, and SUNY Health Science Center (possibly billboard?), 1996? (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 35)
      - "SUNY...Ready or not, here they come", January/February 1997 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 36)
      - "Let's Use Our Heads: SUNY-Think of the Possibilities", January/February 1998 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 37)
      - "Handle With Care SUNY, the Future is in Our Hands", January/February 1999 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 38)
      - "OUCH. Cutting $121 Million from SUNY Hurts Us All", January 2000 (Box VIII.3.1.1, Folder 39)
    - Subseries 3.2 - "UUP in the News", 1987-1995; 11.4.2; 0.33
      Compilations produced sporadically in the 1980s and 1990s of news articles "printed in commercial and UUP affiliate publications which reflect the union's activities and interests in communities across the state and in the state capital [as well as] activities that might be useful for information or reprinting in chapter newsletters". When produced, "UUP in the News" was distributed at Delegate Assemblies.
      - "UUP in the News", Spring 1987 (Box VIII.3.2.1, Folder 1)
      - "UUP in the News", Fall 1987-Winter 1988 (Box VIII.3.2.1, Folder 2)
      - "UUP in the News", Fall 1988 (Box VIII.3.2.1, Folder 3)
      - "UUP in the News", Winter 1989 (Box VIII.3.2.1, Folder 4)
      - "UUP in the News", Spring 1989 (Box VIII.3.2.1, Folder 5)
      - "UUP in the News", Winter 1990 (Box VIII.3.2.1, Folder 6)
      - "UUP in the News", May/June 1990 (Box VIII.3.2.1, Folder 7)
      - "UUP in the News", Winter 1991 (Box VIII.3.2.1, Folder 8)
      - "UUP in the News", Spring 1991 (Box VIII.3.2.1, Folder 9)
      - "UUP in the News", Fall 1991 (Box VIII.3.2.1, Folder 10)
      - "UUP in the News", Spring 1995 (Box VIII.3.2.1, Folder 11)
    - Subseries 3.3 - Other Publications, 1978-2000; 11.4.3; 0.50
      Programs; task force reports, brochures for members, scholarships, and awards; and other printed materials used for both internal purposes and to publicly disseminate UUP's mission and positions on various issues. Some of the materials in this subseries were not actually produced by UUP's Communications Department, but have been grouped here for ease of access. Some of the materials in this subseries are also found with the memorabilia in Series 9 of this Subgroup. Tentative dates were assigned for some of the materials in this subseries based on information provided by members of UUP's Communications Department.
      - The Active Retiree (newsletter), various issues, 1994-1997; 1999-2000 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 1)
      - "Are you concerned about the future of SUNY?"-brochure for Master Plan teleconference, December 5, 1989 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 2)
      - Benefits Brochures/Employee Benefits Handbooks, 1981-1991 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 3)
      - "Celebrating 25 Years of United University Professions/10 Years of Eugene P. Link Scholarship Trust Fund Awards" Program, Fall 1998 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 4)
      - Chapter Treasurers' Handbook, October 1989 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 4A)
      - "Colleagues in Reform"-Conference Report of Task Force on Teacher Education, July 1988 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 5)
      - "Confronting the Changing Academy", by William E. Scheuerman, presented at AFT Higher Education Issues Conference, April 4, 1997 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 5A)
      - "Dollars & Sense-Responding to Attacks on Teachers' Salaries" (NYSUT publication), February 1996 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 6)
      - Eugene P. Link Award Program, May 1986 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 7)
      - Eugene P. Link Scholarship Brochures, 1986-1997 (various years) (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 8)
      - "For the Common Health: A UUP View of SUNY and the Health Sciences", December 1991 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 9)
      - Friend of SUNY Award programs, 1990-2000 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 10)
      - Grapes Boycott Sticker, December 1988 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 11)
      - Group Life Insurance Plan, ca. 1987-1988 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 12)
      - "Helen M. Sackett-In Memoriam", November 20, 1998 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 13)
      - "I'm SUNY and I Vote", bumper sticker, February 1996 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 14)
      - Insurance calling card, undated (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 15)
      - "Is New York's Public University System Becoming Too Private?" brochure, ca. 1988-1989 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 16)
      - Interim Report of Vice President for Academics William E. Scheuerman, November 14, 1989 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 16A)
      - Leadership Handbook, 1988-1989 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 17)
      - Leadership Handbook Updates, 1994-1995 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 18)
      - Leadership Handbook Update-Grievance Section, January 1995 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 19)
      - "Legislative Alert" (newsletter of Legislation Committee Chair Janet L. Potter), March 1988-August 1989; January-July 1992 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 19A)
      - Legislative Breakfast Programs and Invitations, 1989-1992 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 20)
      - Legislative Session Calendar poster, 1996 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 21)
        Original in Box VIII.9.3.
      - Legislative Campaigns (miscellaneous), 1989-1993 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 22)
      - Legislative Forum brochure, March 15, 1989 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 22A)
      - 1999-2000 Legislative Program, January 1999 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 23)
      - 2000 Legislative Program, November 1999 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 24)
      - "Making the News/Framing the Message" (NYSUT local leaders guide to handling the news media), ca. early 1990s (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 25)
      - Membership Brochures, ca. 1988-1989; 1994-1996; 1998 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 26)
      - "The Membership Network" (newsletter of Membership Development Officer Janet L. Potter), nos. 1-2, 4-6, September 1990-March 1991 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 26A)
      - "Myth vs. Reality-The facts show it pays to invest in SUNY", brochure used at Legislative Breakfast, January/February 1991 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 27)
      - "New York Won't Work Without SUNY" bumper sticker (Coalition for Public Higher Education), ca. Fall 1997 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 28)
      - Nina Mitchell Award for Distinguished Service brochures, 1989-1999 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 29)
      - "Nurse Links" (newsletter from UUP Nursing Profession Work Group), March 1991 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 30)
      - "NYSUT-UUP Growing Stronger Through VOTE/COPE", undated (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 31)
      - "On the Relocation of Educational Opportunity Centers to the Department of Labor", April 1996 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 32)
      - Operation Safeguard SUNY, November-December 1997 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 33)
      - PACE (Project for Adult College Education), ca. 1978-1981 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 33A)
      - Pocket Calendars, 1986-1992; 1999-2001 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 34)
      - President Bios (Reilly, Scheuerman), 1990; 1993 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 35)
      - Reilly Statements (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 35A)
        "Viewpoint: Of Pension Peril and Pettifoggery", undated; "UUP Leadership Update", November 8, 1989; and "An Open Letter to the Board of Trustees" (re: parking fees), May 22, 1990.
      - Report of the Task Force on Teacher Education, ca. 1988? (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 36)
      - Retiree Benefits and Membership Application brochures, 1988-1990s (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 37)
      - "Slashed Budget: Declining Access and a Dramatic Economic Effect", 1989 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 38)
      - "SUNY's Colleges of Technology and Agricultural and Technical Colleges-Hands-On Education for the 21st Century", ca. 1993 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 39)
      - "SUNY's Economic Impact", ca. 1987/1988 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 40)
      - "SUNY's Future: Expanding the Mission, Fulfilling the Promise", March 1990 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 41)
      - Task Force on Teacher Education Invitational Conference program, "Continuing the Dialogue: Teacher Education in an Era of Reform", April 22-23, 1988 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 42)
      - Task Force Report on SUNY's Colleges of Technology, 1993 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 43)
        2 difference versions (cover/layout).
      - "A Tribute to Nuala McGann Drescher" program, May 12, 1987 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 44)
      - "A Tribute to John M. Reilly" program, May 18, 1993 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 45)
      - 20th Anniversary Program, 1993 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 46)
      - "25 Years"-Anniversary Review of UUP, 1998 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 47)
      - 25th Anniversary congratulatory photograph signed by Brett Bodine (NASCAR race driver), ca. 1998 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 47)
      - "The Unfinished University: A Story of Disinvestment at the State University of New York", May 1992 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 48)
      - Unity Statement with CSEA, PEF, and Council 82, ca. January-February 1991 (Box VIII.3.3.1, Folder 49)
      - universitas, Vol. 1, nos. 1-4, September 1978-June 1979 (Box VIII.3.3.2, Folder 0)
      - UUP Constitution and Bylaws, April 1978 (Box VIII.3.3.2, Folder 1)
      - UUP Constitution as adopted February 1981 (Box VIII.3.3.2, Folder 2)
      - UUP Constitution-Various Addenda, ca. 1982-1991 (Box VIII.3.3.2, Folder 3)
      - UUP Constitution as amended through 1985 Fall Delegate Assembly (Box VIII.3.3.2, Folder 3A)
      - UUP Constitution as amended through 1987 Winter Delegate Assembly, with February 1988 addendum (Box VIII.3.3.2, Folder 4)
      - UUP Constitution, as amended through the 1989 Winter Delegate Assembly (Box VIII.3.3.2, Folder 5)
      - UUP Constitution as amended through 1993 Winter Delegate Assembly (Box VIII.3.3.2, Folder 6)
      - UUP Fact Sheet, ca. 1990 (Box VIII.3.3.2, Folder 7)
      - UUP Guide to a Healthy Home, ca. July 1995 (Box VIII.3.3.2, Folder 7A)
      - UUP Policy Manual--Policies of the Executive Board and Delegate Assembly, May 1973-November 1986 (Box VIII.3.3.2, Folder 7B)